(Penny:)- Our soup of the day...
- You must release me from my oath.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm working.
Why don't you take a minute to decide?
(Sheldon:)I can't keep your secret, Penny.
I'm going to fold like an energy-based
de novo protein in conformational space.
(Sheldon:)Like a Renaissance triptych.
(Sheldon:)Like a cheap suit.
(Penny:)Look, why is it so hard
for you to keep one little secret?
(Sheldon:)I'm constitutionally incapable.
(Sheldon:)That's why I was refused clearance
for a government research fellowship...
(Sheldon:)...at a secret military supercollider
beneath a fake agricultural station...
...12.5 miles southeast
of Traverse City, Michigan.
(Sheldon:)Which you did not hear about from me.
(Penny:)Look, just forget I told you about me...
(Penny:)...not graduating
from community college, okay?
Forget? You want me to forget?
This mind does not forget.
I haven't forgotten a thing since the day
my mother stopped breastfeeding me.